we need to
output the factorial of numbers five
six seven and eight so let's begin with
five
the factorial is the product of the
given number and
all positive integers less than that
number the factorial of five
would be the product of all positive
integers
less than or equal to five
i'm going to invoke put s as we want to
output the result of this operation
and we're going to count from 5
down to 1 and multiply them all together
the product of this operation will be
the factorial of five
and we see the correct result the
factorial of five
is one hundred and twenty
now that we know how to calculate the
factorial
the rest of this exercise is simple
we also want to output the factorial of
six
the factorial of seven
and the factorial of eight
and you can see that we've successfully
calculated
and output each factorial